In the library window, double-click to open the Practice Files folder.
Find the E-Connected Empower Sleeve Simulation file in E-Fixes.
Double-click on the Connected Empower Sleeve Simulation file.
Or insert it into the 2D or 3D window.
Open the simulation. The sleeve near the wrist is not suitable for wearing after the simulation.
Press A.
In the 3D tool bar, select the Connected Empower Sleeve tool.
In the 2D and 3D window, the grid will be displayed in blue.
If you need to make a precise selection, you can select the grid near the incorrect wearing.
The grid in the selected area will be displayed in green.
In the 2D window, you can check it at the same time.
Use the 3D tool in the selected grid to select the grid near the selected grid.
Press Shift to select more.
In the 3D window, use the positioning tool to move it.
Press A to make it wrap around the model wrist.
Press B.
Open the file and take a look at the 3D window.
Press B to make it open.
Press A.
In the 3D window, select the 3D model and use the positioning tool.
Use the positioning ball tool to rotate and move the sleeve plate to ensure that the sleeve plate is completely wrapped around the wrist of the virtual model.
Do the same on the other side.
The sleeve will be wrapped around the wrist of the virtual model.
Same for the other side.
Move the sleeve at the beginning of each part and place it on the sleeve.
To fix the sleeve on the front side of the ball tree,
adjust the sleeve position from the Давайrench point in front to the heel point.